<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CP on FalconBlog</title>
    <link>https://falconspy6015.github.io/tags/cp/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CP on FalconBlog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://falconspy6015.github.io/tags/cp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Day 17</title>
      <link>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/june/day17/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/june/day17/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;-june-17-2025--tuesday&#34;&gt;📅 June 17, 2025 – Tuesday&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tried Fixing a Stop Point in the Startup Work via Proxy&lt;/strong&gt;: Attempted to resolve a critical issue in the startup project by experimenting with proxy setups. Unfortunately, it didn’t work, but the effort contributed to my understanding of network routing and limitations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Div 3 Codeforces Contest&lt;/strong&gt;: Participated in a Division 3 CP contest. Gave it my best and picked up several key fundaes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Took CP Fundae from Senior&lt;/strong&gt;: Had a discussion with a senior who shared invaluable tips and strategies to improve in competitive programming. Grateful for the mentorship.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another day filled with learning through failure, contest participation, and mentorship.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 12</title>
      <link>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/june/day12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/june/day12/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;-june-12-2025--thursday&#34;&gt;📅 June 12, 2025 – Thursday&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Second CP Contest&lt;/strong&gt;: Participated in another competitive programming contest to sharpen my problem-solving skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drafted Team Meeting Agenda&lt;/strong&gt;: Outlined the key discussion points for the upcoming team meeting to ensure smooth communication.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Configured Notion for Team Collaboration&lt;/strong&gt;: Set up and organized the team’s Notion workspace with project docs, task lists, and resource links for seamless coordination.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 8</title>
      <link>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/june/day8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/june/day8/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;-june-8-2025--sunday&#34;&gt;🚀 June 8, 2025 – Sunday&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Attended First Ever CP Contest&lt;/strong&gt;: Participated in my first competitive programming contest. It was a thrilling experience that gave me insight into real-time problem-solving under pressure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documented the Experience on GitHub&lt;/strong&gt;: Made a log of the contest, what I solved, and what I learned. This helps track progress and reflect on areas for improvement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Tenure as Co-Lead Begins&lt;/strong&gt;: Officially stepped into the role of project Co-Lead. Started organizing initial thoughts and planning out the first steps for the new responsibilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
