<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Startup on FalconBlog</title>
    <link>https://falconspy6015.github.io/tags/startup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Startup on FalconBlog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://falconspy6015.github.io/tags/startup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Day 24</title>
      <link>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/june/day24/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/june/day24/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;-june-24-2025--tuesday&#34;&gt;📅 June 24, 2025 – Tuesday&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stereo Camera Setup&lt;/strong&gt;: Worked hands-on with the stereo cam configuration for the &lt;strong&gt;startup project&lt;/strong&gt;. Focused on tuning parameters and verifying setup stability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Discussions&lt;/strong&gt;: Had an in-depth discussion with the &lt;strong&gt;team lead&lt;/strong&gt; regarding important updates and milestones. Planning for the next sprint began.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive Programming&lt;/strong&gt;: Spent time learning new &lt;strong&gt;CP tactics&lt;/strong&gt;, reinforcing problem-solving techniques, and brushing up concepts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of those solid days of technical work, strategic planning, and personal growth.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 17</title>
      <link>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/june/day17/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/june/day17/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;-june-17-2025--tuesday&#34;&gt;📅 June 17, 2025 – Tuesday&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tried Fixing a Stop Point in the Startup Work via Proxy&lt;/strong&gt;: Attempted to resolve a critical issue in the startup project by experimenting with proxy setups. Unfortunately, it didn’t work, but the effort contributed to my understanding of network routing and limitations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Div 3 Codeforces Contest&lt;/strong&gt;: Participated in a Division 3 CP contest. Gave it my best and picked up several key fundaes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Took CP Fundae from Senior&lt;/strong&gt;: Had a discussion with a senior who shared invaluable tips and strategies to improve in competitive programming. Grateful for the mentorship.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another day filled with learning through failure, contest participation, and mentorship.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 7</title>
      <link>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/june/day7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/june/day7/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;-june-7-2025--saturday&#34;&gt;🛠️ June 7, 2025 – Saturday&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Finalised Work at the Startup&lt;/strong&gt;: Wrapped up remaining tasks and confirmed final deliverables. Marked the end of an exciting and educational phase.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Attended Co-Lead Interview&lt;/strong&gt;: Gave my best in the project co-lead interview. Shared my past contributions and vision for future responsibilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Debugged TightVNC Issues&lt;/strong&gt;: Faced connection problems with TightVNC. Managed to troubleshoot and resolve them successfully.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documented Progress in GitHub&lt;/strong&gt;: Pushed recent technical achievements and notes to GitHub to ensure everything stays tracked and organized.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Travelled Back Home&lt;/strong&gt;: Made the journey back home smoothly. Used the time to reflect and plan next steps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
