<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal-Growth on FalconBlog</title>
    <link>https://falconspy6015.github.io/tags/personal-growth/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal-Growth on FalconBlog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://falconspy6015.github.io/tags/personal-growth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Day 8</title>
      <link>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/day-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/day-8/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;january-8-2025---a-carnival-of-culture-and-creativity&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;January 8, 2025 - A Carnival of Culture and Creativity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today marked &lt;strong&gt;Day 0&lt;/strong&gt; of &lt;strong&gt;Saarang&lt;/strong&gt;, our much-awaited cultural fest, and it was a day brimming with excitement, camaraderie, and awe-inspiring experiences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;exploring-stalls-a-vibrant-start&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exploring Stalls: A Vibrant Start&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The day kicked off with a visit to the fest stalls alongside my friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There were countless &lt;strong&gt;food stalls&lt;/strong&gt;, far more than we had during our tech fest. The aromas and diversity of flavors were captivating.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other stalls showcased &lt;strong&gt;aesthetic items&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;rings&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;accessories&lt;/strong&gt;, and exclusive &lt;strong&gt;merchandise&lt;/strong&gt; that added to the festival charm.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Book lovers were not left out, with &lt;strong&gt;bookstalls&lt;/strong&gt; lining the lanes, offering treasures for the avid reader.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I also noticed preparations for a &lt;strong&gt;carnival-like atmosphere&lt;/strong&gt;, with towering structures like a &lt;strong&gt;Ferris wheel&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;huge swings&lt;/strong&gt; being built. The festive energy was undeniable!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;drama-and-theatrics-performances-that-inspire&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drama and Theatrics: Performances That Inspire&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, I headed to the &lt;strong&gt;CLT Lawns (Central Lecture Theatre)&lt;/strong&gt; to witness a &lt;strong&gt;drama competition&lt;/strong&gt; featuring performances from various colleges.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 7</title>
      <link>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/day-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/day-7/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;January 7, 2025 - A Day of Cybersecurity, Celebrations, and Comfort&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today was an exciting journey of learning and preparation, offering a perfect balance between intellectual challenges and personal organization.
Ethical Hacking Workshop: Unveiling Cyber Secrets&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The day began with a fascinating Ethical Hacking Workshop that featured two in-depth sessions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Session 1 (9:00 AM - 12:00 PM): Focused on the basics of ethical hacking, emphasizing methodologies and tools used to identify and mitigate vulnerabilities.
Session 2 (2:00 PM - 5:00 PM): Took a deeper dive into advanced hacking techniques, offering hands-on exercises to strengthen our understanding of cyber defense mechanisms.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The workshop wasn’t just about learning to break into systems but understanding how to protect them. It was both enlightening and empowering.
Diving Into CTF Challenges&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 6</title>
      <link>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/day-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/day-6/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;january-6-2025---a-day-of-insights-entertainment-and-delights&#34;&gt;January 6, 2025 - A Day of Insights, Entertainment, and Delights&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blockchain Workshop: Learning the Technology of Tomorrow&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The day began with a highly informative Blockchain Workshop that spanned across two engaging sessions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Session 1 (9:00 AM - 12:00 PM): Focused on the fundamentals of blockchain technology, its architecture, and applications.
Session 2 (2:00 PM - 5:00 PM): Built on the foundation laid earlier, diving into smart contracts and decentralized applications. The workshop provided a great mix of theory and hands-on experience, helping me gain a clearer perspective on blockchain&#39;s immense potential.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spectacular Envisage Show at the SAC&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 5</title>
      <link>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/day-5/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;january-5-2025---a-day-of-learning-exploration-and-celebration&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;January 5, 2025 - A Day of Learning, Exploration, and Celebration&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;focused-study-on-vector-spaces&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Focused Study on Vector Spaces&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The day began with an intense &lt;strong&gt;90-minute math session&lt;/strong&gt;, during which I delved deeper into topics related to vector spaces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Learnings&lt;/strong&gt;: Linear dependence, linear combination, span of a vector subspace, and their core properties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources Used&lt;/strong&gt;: Referred to multiple books from our library and supplemented the reading with &lt;strong&gt;NPTEL lectures&lt;/strong&gt; for added clarity. This session helped solidify my conceptual understanding of the subject.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;stall-exploration-and-puzzle-challenges&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stall Exploration and Puzzle Challenges&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the afternoon, I decided to unwind a bit by exploring the event stalls on campus.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 4</title>
      <link>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/day-4/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;january-4-2025---a-day-of-iot-linear-algebra-and-electrifying-robotics&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;January 4, 2025 - A Day of IoT, Linear Algebra, and Electrifying Robotics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IoT Workshop - Raspberry Pi&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The day kicked off with an inspiring IoT workshop centred around the versatile Raspberry Pi. Split into two sessions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Morning (9:00 AM - 12:00 PM)&lt;/strong&gt;: We explored foundational IoT concepts and set up the Raspberry Pi for various applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Afternoon (2:00 PM - 5:00 PM)&lt;/strong&gt;: This session focused on real-world IoT projects and experimentation, which deepened my understanding and excitement for this growing field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Library Study Time: Vector Spaces and Subspaces&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
From &lt;strong&gt;5:00 PM to 6:30 PM&lt;/strong&gt;, I tucked myself away in the library for a focused study session on vector spaces and subspaces in linear algebra. The clarity I gained during this time was immensely satisfying.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 3</title>
      <link>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/day-3/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;todays-progress---january-3-2025&#34;&gt;Today&amp;rsquo;s Progress - January 3, 2025&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Successfully Passed Driving Test&lt;/strong&gt;: Thrilled to have earned my driving license today! It was an amazing experience, and all the practice finally paid off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Boarded Train and Met Classmate&lt;/strong&gt;: During the journey, I caught up with a classmate. We had an enriching discussion and learned more about neural networks, Support Vector Machines (SVM), and tools like Zettelkasten in Obsidian.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Arrived at Campus&lt;/strong&gt;: Got picked up by my cousin upon arrival, reached IIT Madras, and settled into my room.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 2</title>
      <link>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/day-2/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;todays-progress---january-2-2025&#34;&gt;Today&amp;rsquo;s Progress - January 2, 2025&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Driving Lesson in the Morning&lt;/strong&gt;: Completed the final driving lesson today in preparation for tomorrow’s driving test. Feeling confident and excited about earning my license approval.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Last-Minute Packing&lt;/strong&gt;: Finished all last-minute packing for the journey back to campus. Ensured that everything is organized and ready for a smooth transition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quality Time with Mom and Dad&lt;/strong&gt;: Spent meaningful moments with my parents as they gave me their final thoughts and advice before I leave for the semester. Grateful for their support and encouragement.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1</title>
      <link>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://falconspy6015.github.io/journal/day-1/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;todays-progress&#34;&gt;Today&amp;rsquo;s Progress:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Completed ROS 2 4-wheeled robot simulation in Gazebo&lt;/strong&gt;: Spent time configuring and simulating a robot model using Gazebo. It was an exciting hands-on experience, and I&amp;rsquo;m glad to see it working.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Set up my journal for the new year&lt;/strong&gt;: Dedicated some time today to create a fresh journal layout for 2025. This will help keep my daily progress and thoughts organized for the upcoming semester.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shifted my laptop&lt;/strong&gt;: Moved everything from my old system to my new one, ensuring that all my data and files are ready for the next phase of work. Everything’s now set up for easy access when I return to campus.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Year New Me</title>
      <link>https://falconspy6015.github.io/posts/new-year-new-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://falconspy6015.github.io/posts/new-year-new-me/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;a-new-year-a-new-vision&#34;&gt;A New Year, A New Vision&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the new year unfolds, I&amp;rsquo;m reflecting on the journey so far and looking ahead to the exciting challenges and opportunities to come.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;academics-and-aspirations&#34;&gt;Academics and Aspirations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My focus remains on excelling in electrical engineering at IITM, diving deeper into semiconductor specialization, and staying aligned with my goal of securing a top-tier placement at companies like NVIDIA, Intel, and Amazon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Beyond academics, I aim to sharpen my competitive programming skills, mastering problem-solving to stand out in tech challenges.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;building-and-innovating&#34;&gt;Building and Innovating&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I’ve made strides in personal projects, from developing apps like Florafix to diving into open-source and honing my web development skills with frameworks like Hugo.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CTF challenges and exploring cybersecurity continue to expand my skill set and fuel my curiosity for problem-solving.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;health-habits-and-growth&#34;&gt;Health, Habits, and Growth&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discipline in routines like morning study sessions and mindful eating remain key to balancing my ambitions with personal well-being.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Music, podcasts, and meaningful interactions are helping me stay relaxed and creative.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-road-ahead&#34;&gt;The Road Ahead&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2025 is about building momentum toward becoming financially stable and striving for excellence in all my endeavors, whether it&amp;rsquo;s academics, projects, or personal growth. It&amp;rsquo;s another step closer to the big dream of making an impact and supporting my family.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
